listingware.com 2009-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Real Estate IDX, Website and Mobile Solutions

Privacy Policy

We demonstrate our commitment to our customers' privacy by providing this policy. We will do everything in our power to ensure your right to privacy. We are committed to developing long-lasting relationships that are built on trust. We will never violate that trust. 

**Personal Data Transmissions Are Encrypted**  
When you order from us, all your personal information is protected. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry standard, for encrypting all personal information, including name, address and credit card numbers. 

**Online Ordering Optional**  
If you feel uncomfortable with the online ordering process, We offers the option of calling us toll-free at 800.867.4707 for ordering accounts. 

**We Will Not Sell Your Personal Information**  
We keeps all your information confidential. 

**Collection and Storage of Third-Party Information**  
Because part of our service is based upon collecting and storing data relating to our Customers' Customers, we are especially sensitive to privacy! Any data related to the individual web site visitors of our Customers will only be visible to that individual Customer of ours and will only contain information relevant to the services that our Customer will provide to their web site visitors. 

**Policy Changes**  
We are dedicated to providing the best service possible to every one of our clients. We are also dedicated to staying on top of available technology. 

While we will provide our clients with reasonable notification, we reserve the right to change its policy at any time to meet the needs of our Customers, their web site visitors, changing laws and new technology. 

We understands that many of you are concerned about cookies. We provide this Cookie Policy Statement to let you know how we use this technology. We use cookies to help us improve our website and listings search engine services, and, most importantly, provide our existing customers with the opportunity for continued savings and increased convenience. 

**Cookies For Improving Our Web Site**  
We use cookies to inform us of a repeat visit. The cookie does not tell us who you are, your name, email address, or Passwords. 

**Cookies For Customer Account Management**  
For our customers, we use cookies to store usernames for added convenience to the you and the Webmaster. As part of our service packages, we offer password-protected web-based management tools. By storing the customers' Usernames in a cookie, the Webmaster will not have to keep filling out form fields when they desire to manage their account. (The cookie does not store Passwords.) we are dedicated to using the newest technologies in order to simplify our customers' lives. 

**Cookies For Displaying Customers' Accounts**  
Because our business is hosting web pages that display information in the name of and branded to our Customers, we use temporary cookies (also referred to as "Session Cookies") to hold the settings of the web pages that are shown to their web site visitors. These temporary cookies hold information simply to keep track of how our Customers' web sites should appear, such as their pictures, logos, layout and color schemes.   
  
**ListingWare** provides Internet Data Exchange (IDX), Broker Reciprocity, Internet Listings Display (ILD),  
and Virtual Office Websites (VOW) for thousands of Real Estate Agents and Brokers nationwide,   
as well as complete template-based, enhanced, and custom website and mobile solutions, all with our exclusive API.
